[
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "major1",
    "a1": "Augmented",
    "a2": "Diminished",
    "a3": "Major",
    "a4": "Minor",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "minor1",
    "a1": "Minor",
    "a2": "Diminished",
    "a3": "Major",
    "a4": "Augmented",
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "diminished1",
    "a1": "Major",
    "a2": "Minor",
    "a3": "Augmented",
    "a4": "Diminished",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "augmented1",
    "a1": "Minor",
    "a2": "Augmented",
    "a3": "Major",
    "a4": "Diminished",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "major2",
    "a1": "Diminished",
    "a2": "Minor",
    "a3": "Augmented",
    "a4": "Major",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "diminished2",
    "a1": "Augmented",
    "a2": "Major",
    "a3": "Diminished",
    "a4": "Minor",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "minor2",
    "a1": "Minor",
    "a2": "Diminished",
    "a3": "Major",
    "a4": "Augmented",
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "minor3",
    "a1": "Major",
    "a2": "Minor",
    "a3": "Augmented",
    "a4": "Diminished",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "major3",
    "a1": "Major",
    "a2": "Augmented",
    "a3": "Diminished",
    "a4": "Minor",
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "augmented2",
    "a1": "Diminished",
    "a2": "Major",
    "a3": "Minor",
    "a4": "Augmented",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "major4",
    "a1": "Augmented",
    "a2": "Diminished",
    "a3": "Major",
    "a4": "Minor",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of triad is this?",
    "interval": "minor4",
    "a1": "Major",
    "a2": "Minor",
    "a3": "Augmented",
    "a4": "Diminished",
    "correct": "2"
  }
]